[{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"How can college students resist the desire to buy more and more goodies?","answerOptions":["Set a budget","Practice self-control","Shop with a list","Avoid impulsive buying"],"answer":"All of the above","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"True or False: Consuming bad stuff like junk food can negatively impact academic performance.","answerOptions":["True","False"],"answer":"True","type":"true/false","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"What can college students do to avoid getting sick?","answerOptions":["Wash hands frequently","Get enough rest","Eat nutritious foods","Exercise regularly"],"answer":"All of the above","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"Are tissues necessary to have in a college dorm room?","answerOptions":["Yes","No"],"answer":"Yes","type":"true/false","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"Why is it important for college students to manage stress effectively?","answerOptions":["To improve mental health","To enhance academic performance","To maintain physical well-being","To promote overall well-being"],"answer":"All of the above","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"True or False: Bad stuff like procrastination can lead to academic problems.","answerOptions":["True","False"],"answer":"True","type":"true/false","hardness":"easy","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"A practical way to organize study materials is by using ____________.","answer":"folders","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"When facing a difficult situation, college students should seek support from ____________.","answer":"friends and family","type":"fill in the blank","hardness":"medium","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"What is a common consequence of consuming too much caffeine?","answerOptions":["Difficulty sleeping","Increased heart rate","Jitters","Headaches"],"answer":"All of the above","type":"multiple choice","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1},{"id":"lsvdcuun","question":"True or False: Using alcohol to cope with stress is a healthy approach.","answerOptions":["True","False"],"answer":"False","type":"true/false","hardness":"hard","marksWorth":1}]